<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<generator>Mixture</generator>
		<title>Neil Kinnish : Articles</title>
		<link>http://neilkinnish.com
		<description>Previously TAK! now... Developer / Creative / Consultant. Currently meddling with new technology and ideas. Co-founder @teammixture @workfu.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<webmaster>hello@neilkinnish.com</webmaster>
		<copyright>&amp;copy;2013 Neil Kinnish</copyright>
		<pubdate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 12:17:05 GMT</pubdate>
		<lastbuilddate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 12:17:05 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		
			<item>
	<title>Mixture updates</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/mixture-updates
	<guid>/article/mixture-updates</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Wed, 15 May 2013 10:56:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>We&amp;#8217;ve just pushed some updates to Mixture, this is quite a big release featuring a number of new additions and improvements I&amp;#8217;ve decided to log the main points here&amp;#8230;
Collections
This is the biggest feature addition and essentially brings the power of blogging and much more to Mixture.
Inspired by tools like Jekyll,...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Taking stock...</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/taking-stock
	<guid>/article/taking-stock</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 13:59:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>We&amp;#8217;ve been progressing very quickly with Mixture over the last few months, today I decided to stop, breathe and make a quick log of where Mixture is today and whats coming next.
It&amp;#8217;s nice to write down our progress, we&amp;#8217;ve come a very long way since the original alpha app we...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Small but important updates</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/small-but-important-updates
	<guid>/article/small-but-important-updates</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 23:26:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>If you&amp;#8217;re using Mixture you may have noticed we are pushing updates continuously, improvements, fixes and new features.
We&amp;#8217;ve just made another small but powerful update.
Mixture currently has two project types (or modes) &amp;#8220;Mixture&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;Simple&amp;#8221;.
A Mixture project benefits from all of the features and functionality that the tool and online...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>It&#39;s all about HTML &amp; Includes</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/its-all-about-html-includes
	<guid>/article/its-all-about-html-includes</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 16:36:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>Over the last few months I&amp;#8217;ve read various conversations on Twitter and listened to podcast discussions regarding HTML and specifically template engines, the main gist of this conversation&amp;#8230;

&amp;#8220;I just want to use HTML but with includes&amp;#8221;

&amp;#8230;and&amp;#8230;

&amp;#8220;I don&amp;#8217;t want to learn a new template language&amp;#8221;

And of course we&amp;#8217;ve had similar comments...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Building</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/building
	<guid>/article/building</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 09:34:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>
Over the last few months we&amp;#8217;ve been building and alpha testing Mixture.
Wednesday (20th) we opened it up and moved into public beta, we&amp;#8217;ve by no means finished, in fact we&amp;#8217;re just getting warmed up. We have lots to do and lots planned&amp;#8230; I really can&amp;#8217;t wait to show some of...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Live refresh &amp; Multi-device testing, any type of project</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/live-refresh-multi-device-testing-any-type-of
	<guid>/article/live-refresh-multi-device-testing-any-type-of</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 19:20:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>We are literally days away from releasing the public beta version of Mixture and we&amp;#8217;ve added a feature that we&amp;#8217;re pretty excited about.
When using Mixture to build a standard Mixture project you can already multi-device test with Mixture&amp;#8217;s local server, it will even live refresh and style inject for you...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Project insights</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/project-insights
	<guid>/article/project-insights</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 10:35:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>Over the last couple of weeks I&amp;#8217;ve been working on the new Future Insights site with Mike Kus.
I&amp;#8217;ve decided to detail some of our decisions as they may be useful.
I&amp;#8217;ve worked on a few responsive sites and taken various approaches, some good and some bad, as always the decisions you...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Mixture pricing &amp; plans</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/mixture-pricing-plans
	<guid>/article/mixture-pricing-plans</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 15:35:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>Over the last few weeks people have been asking about the pricing and release schedule for Mixture.
We&amp;#8217;re currently working very hard to get everything in place so as we can release the public beta of Mixture late Feb / early Match. Whilst in beta Mixture will be free to use...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Mixture build + screencasts</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/mixture-build-screencasts
	<guid>/article/mixture-build-screencasts</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 11:20:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>As of today I am going to begin building the front-end templates for Mixture&amp;#8217;s registration, account management &amp;amp; public profiles (screenshots below). These will be the real templates used when we open up access to Mixture - currently planned for the end of January / early February.
I thought it would...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Is there an appetite for front-end dev tools on Windows?</title>
	<link>http://neilkinnish.com/article/is-there-an-appetite-for-front-end-dev-tools-on
	<guid>/article/is-there-an-appetite-for-front-end-dev-tools-on</guid>
	
	<pubdate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 13:35:00 GMT</pubdate>
	<description>Over the last few months we have been actively building Mixture for the Mac &amp;amp; Windows platforms - it has always been our aim to support both.
However, over the last couple of months while previewing the application, we&amp;#8217;ve begun to question the appetite for tools like Mixture on the Windows...</description>
</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>